MORGAN KIGER

Software Developer

• DETAILS •

mkiger95@gmail.com

• LINKS •

Github

LinkedIn

www.morgankiger.com

∘ SKILLS ∘

SQL Database Creative Thinker Agile Methodologies Linux/Command Prompt Efficient Time Management Requires Minimal Supervision

PROFILE

I am computer engineering student with a minor in math and computer science. I have **2 years of experience** in developing, automation, data reconciliation, SQL databases, and more. Over the years I have led and delivered successful agile-structured projects.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer at Bonotel Exlcusive Travel

October 2018 - Present

- Coded automation for data entry process within the business
- Coded an automated inventory check that checks availability for all active hotels weekly
- Built a status page for all of our internal apps for internal staff to view
- Coded an automated data recon between our booking and billing application

IT Intern at Bonotel Exclusive Travel

December 2015 - October 2018

- Mapped hotels to our system, to create a real-time connection for rates
- Supported all of internal staff with anything tech related

Guest Services/Reservations Agent at Bonotel Exclusive Travel

April 2015 - December 2015

- Handled customer issues in a gracious manner and in accordance with company policies.
- Answered phone calls, liaison between hotel and partner, sold/booked hotel rooms

Shift Manager at Sweet Addiction

August 2012 - May 2014

- Supervised staff and handled all customer service issues
- Handled all money/till at the end of the day, ultimately ran the shop

EDUCATION

University of Nevada Las Vegas

August 2014 - Present

Degree: Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

- Minor in Computer Science and Mathematics
- Member of Lambda Chi Alpha
 - o Held position: President, Secretary, Alumni Relations

West Career & Technical Academy

August 2010 - May 2014

Degree: Business Management

- Advanced Honors Dipolma
- Competed in Future Business Leaders of America's National Competition for two years.
 Received an award for placing 3rd.